<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<event>
    <id>2014100401</id>
    <title>Canadian Investment and Financing Workshop - International Trade - Episode One</title>
    <date>Oct 4th, 2014</date>
    <body>
        <p>October 4, 2014, Toronto – Canada China Capital Market Access Corporate (CCCMAC), a Toronto-Based non-for-profit organization, hosted the “International Trade” second seminar successfully in Markham on Saturday. President Ms. Jessica Zhang, CFA and VP Marketing Ms. Cynthia Yu, CGA, CFA, invited more than 30 business leaders and professionals to attend this event and share their industry insights among the group.</p>
        <p>Mr. Kevin Sullivan, Account Manager for Commercial Markets and Small Business at Export Development Canada (EDC), delivered an excellent presentation on the Account Receivable Insurance. The product not only can help international business owners to protect their account receivables, but also helps raise more working capital from the banks. With his extensive experience and real life cases, the audiences gained more knowledge in terms of how EDC can export business. One of Mr. Sullivan’s clients, a well-know Chinese food import &amp; export company, also shared their own expense of working with EDC and BMO on accounts receivable financing.</p>
        <p>Ms. Tina Yu, VP Foreign Exchange Products at Bank of Montreal (BMO), and Mr. Mo Yang, CA, Associate Commercial Services Group at Bank of Montreal, provided a detailed introduction on foreign exchange capital market products and global view on foreign exchange. Ms. Tina Yu mentioned the latest promotion on their leading online Banking for Foreign Exchange. Later, Mr. Mo Yang demonstrated how the US economy, employment and commodities factors contributing to a recent strong USD. As global economic uncertainty continues, he answered some questions on how banks can add value by recommending the right trades facilities to hedge FX exposure. After the two informative speeches, the audiences were discussing over the key topics and asked many questions from their own experience. All the participants had the chance to network with others while enjoying the delicious refreshment.</p>
        <p>This is the fifth Educational seminar organized by Canada China Capital Market Access Corporation (a non-for-profit organization). The goal is to help Canadian Chinese immigrates and businessmen to better understand Canadian capital market structure and find good investment opportunities. You can become a life-time member with only $100. Application form is the following link: &lt;a href="contact.php"&gt;Contact Us&lt;/a&gt;. You will be free to join all the future seminars and access to the global database.</p>
    </body>
</event>
