<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<event>
    <id>2014110401</id>
    <title>BIPB Event Summary</title>
    <date>Nov 4th, 2014</date>
    <body>
        <p>November 4, 2014, Canada China Capital Market Access Corporate (CCCMAC) successfully hosted the BIPB event, which provided a platform for Canadian entrepreneurs to better understand the investment environment in China and initiate relationship with local government and potential strategic partners.</p>
        <p>The director of Beijing Investment Promotion Bureau (BIPB), Mr. Zhou Weimin led the BIPB delegation and joined this event. Representatives from six local companies (Tabl’eau、SSIMWave、Instant Chemistry、Tech Magnesium、Animation Production Studio、MaR）made presentations sequentially and conducted in-depth one-on-one talk with BIPB representatives.</p>
        <p>Tabl’eau first started the meeting with Mr. Zhou over a conference call. Tal’eau is a provider of advanced water filtration and serving systems supplying premium chilled sparkling, still and ambient water to select restaurants, hotels, homes, offices, facilities and events. Tabl’eau commits itself to offer a premium alternative water solution that eliminates the need for traditional packaged waters and their large carbon footprint. It planned to set up a manufacturing facility in China.</p>
        <p>SSIMWave, the second presenter, is a spinoff company from University of Waterloo. In the past decade, the SSIMWave team has made many new breakthroughs upon SSIM in terms of accuracy, speed, applicability and flexibility. The development of leading technologies for video quality monitoring, video quality diagnosis, and perceptual video compression has led to state-of-the-art products for media, communication and entertainment industry. They sought to find a strategic partner and bring the new technology into Chinese market.</p>
        <p>Instant Chemistry is a bio-info technology company that is facilitating the mass user adoption of personal genomics. According to its proprietary research result, people that are biologically compatible are more likely to have stable and healthy relationships. Instant Chemistry successfully commercialized this technology in the Canadian market and planned to expand its business in the even-bigger Chinese market.</p>
        <p>After a short break, Tech Magnesium started its talk with BIPB. This has developed a proprietary, breakthrough technology capable of producing magnesium metal (“Mg”) at a cost that is competitive with aluminum. Based on the results of work to date, Tech Magnesium’s process will have a cost advantage of at least 25% over Chinese Mg producers. Moreover, the process will also dramatically reduce GHG emissions by over 65%. The company representative expressed their interest in meeting more industrial elites and discussing feasibility of cooperation models.</p>
        <p>Mr. Ray Brooks is a renowned angel investor in Canada. As a sponsor of Animation Production Studio, he has raised billions of dollars to expand business in Chinese market. He is interested in building movie themed parks, elderly retirement communities in China and searching Chinese mineral suppliers for Canadian local metal manufacturers.</p>
        <p>Last but not least, MaRS brought several clean energy technology projects. The participants shared their knowledge on the lasts market trends and agreed to have further talks on specific projects in the near future.</p>
        <p>At the end of the meeting, all participants expressed that this event was very helpful for them to gather useful information and initiate relations with key stake holders. They felt more confident about their Chinese market strategies with the support from BIPB.</p>
    </body>
</event>
