<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<event>
    <id>2014100402</id>
    <title>Canadian Investment and Financing Workshop - International Trade - Episode Two</title>
    <date>Oct 4th, 2014</date>
    <body>
        <p>To continue with our series of "Canadian Investment and Financing Workshop", Canada China Capital Market Access presents to you: a seminar on International Trade - Episode Two</p>
        <p>Uncertainty is evident during the operation of international trade business, from the risk of not being able to collect foreign accounts receivables to the fluctuation of different currencies, both at times could impact financial bottom line. How do we find ways to better manage these risks and normalize revenue and net income? Are there any cost-worthy insurance we could purchase and how can my bank offer me ways to hedge foreign exchange risk.</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;For this workshop, we have invited the following seasoned key note speakers:&lt;/span&gt;</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;Mr. Kevin Sullivan&lt;/span&gt;, Account Manager and trade advisor, Export Development Canada&lt;br/&gt;Mr. Sullivan has had extensive experience in international trade prior to EDC, working in China and Germany with multi-national firms. Mr. Sullivan speaks fluent Chinese.</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;Ms. Tina Yu&lt;/span&gt;, VP Foreign Exchange Products, Bank of Montreal&lt;br/&gt;Ms. Yu has over 20 years in BMO Capital market FX team. She represented BMO by providing monthly economic news review on Channel 14 – Omni TV.</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;This workshop will focus on the following:&lt;/span&gt;</p>
        <p>1) What are the different types of Accounts Receivables insurance and how do I use them effectively in my trading business? &lt;br/&gt;2) How can Accounts Receivables insurance help me in bank financing? &lt;br/&gt;3) How could FX risk impact my business? &lt;br/&gt;4) What are the capital market products available to manage currency risk?</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;Date:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Saturday October 4th 2014, 1:30-5pm</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;Venue:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br/&gt;3985 Highway 7 East, Unit 301, Markham</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;Format:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;1:30-2:15pm Networking &amp; round table 
&lt;br/&gt;2:20-2:50pm Presentation by Export Development Canada
&lt;br/&gt;2:55-3:10pm Q&amp;A
&lt;br/&gt;3:15-3:35pm Net working
&lt;br/&gt;3:40-4:10pm Presentation by Bank of Montreal
&lt;br/&gt;4:15-4:30pm Q&amp;A</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;Cost:&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;br/&gt;Free for CCCMAC members; $20 pp. (with one guest at no additional cost)
&lt;br/&gt;Refreshment (snack, fruit, coffee and tea) will be served.</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;Payment Method:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;Cash or Cheque (Payable title on cheque: Canada China Capital Market Access Corp.)
&lt;br/&gt;Maximum: 30 people. Please RSVP by September 23rd, 2014</p>
        <p>&lt;span class="bold"&gt;Contact:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;Ellen Mu 647-887-8215 &lt;a href="mailto:info@cccmac.com"&gt;info@cccmac.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;Cynthia Yu 416-886-5197 &lt;a href="mailto:cynthia@cccmac.com"&gt;cynthia@cccmac.com&lt;/a&gt;</p>
    </body>
</event>