<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<event>
    <id>2015012401</id>
    <title>Due Diligence</title>
    <date>Jan 24th, 2015</date>
    <body>
        <p photo_position="right">Jan 24th, 2015, Toronto – Canada China Capital Market Access Corporate (CCCMAC), a Toronto-Based non-for-profit organization, hosted a seminar on “Due Diligence process on business investment”. President Ms. Jessica Zhang, CFA, founder at Langda Consulting Inc., and VP Marketing Ms. Cynthia Yu, CGA, CFA, Commercial Account Manager in Mid-Market at Bank of Montreal, invited more than 32 business leaders and professionals to attend this event and share their industry insights among the group.</p>
        <p photo_position="left">Ms. Judith Jiang, Partner at Fogler, Rubinoff LLP, delivered an excellent presentation on Legal Due Diligence. Judith first introduced how lawyers in their area of expertise can help the client identify and mitigate the potential risks associated with merger and acquisition. Judith then shared her insight about the advantages and disadvantages of buying assets or shares from the target company. In particular, she discussed, how the lawyers could use their knowledge and experience to help clients identify risks and resolve potential problems from a legal perspective.</p>
        <p photo_position="right">Following a short break after the first presentation, PWC delivered another exceptional presentation about the Finance and Tax due diligence in the Merger and Acquisition activities. First, Mr. Arthur Chan introduced the team structure and global resources of PWC, and elaborated how the firm’s professionals would help ensure their clients success. Mr. John Matheson explained finance due diligence in detail, focusing on how it benefits clients from both buyer and seller sides. Henry then explained tax due diligence and shared examples of how different kinds of tax considerations can impact deals and how the professional teams could help clients on various tax issues in the Merger and Acquisition deals.</p>
        <p photo_position="left">After the two informative presentations, all the participants had the chance to network with others in their areas of interest and share their thoughts and ideas among the group. This is the sixth Educational seminar organized by CCCMAC.</p>
        <p>The goal of our organization is to help Canadian Chinese immigrates and businessmen understand the Canadian capital market structure and identify potential investment opportunities. You can sign up as a formal member with only $100. Application form is the following link: &lt;a href="contact.php"&gt;Contact Us&lt;/a&gt;. As a member of the CCCMAC, you can attend all the upcoming seminars for free and have an access to our global database.</p>
    </body>
    <photos>
        <photo>
            <i>1.jpg</i>
            <d>Jessica Zhang introduce CCCMAC</d>
        </photo>
        <photo>
            <i>2.jpg</i>
            <d>PWC team discuss tax due diligence</d>
        </photo>
        <photo>
            <i>3.jpg</i>
            <d>Judith present legal due diligence</d>
        </photo>
        <photo>
            <i>4.jpg</i>
            <d>Arthur from PWC received gift from CCCMAC</d>
        </photo>
    </photos>
</event>
