<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<event>
    <id>2015030701</id>
    <title>Fundamentals of Real Estate Investment</title>
    <date>Mar 7th, 2015</date>
    <body>
        <p photo_position="right">March 7, 2015, Toronto - Canada China Capital Market Access Corporate (CCCMAC), brought to its members and guests a seminar on “Fundamentals of Real Estate Investment”. More than 30 industry professionals and sophisticated investors attended the seminar and shared their insights with others.</p>
        <p photo_position="left">Mr. Meanchoff, Managing Director and Principal at Lennard Commercial Realty, and Ms. Li, Senior Project Manager at Lennard Commercial Realty, made a joint presentation on the overall picture of commercial real estate investment. There are four types of broad income producing real estate: office, retail, industrial and multi-family residential. They listed top 5 mistakes in investing in this area. The presentation was closed up with five important steps before acquiring real property.</p>
        <p photo_position="right">Following a short networking break, Doug Shinobu, Managing Director at Greengate Capital Corporation, started his presentation on senior housing. He explained why he believes in the future of senior housing, and analyzed the risk and return on various types of senior housing projects. Doug also pointed out two key elements of investing in this niche market: 1) government’s subsidy and 2) operating management’s track record.</p>
        <p photo_position="left">After the two excellent presentations, our members and guests mingled around, asking more specific questions to dig deeper on the topic. This is the seventh educational seminar organized by CCCMAC.</p>
        <p>The goal of our organization is to help Canadian Chinese immigrates and businessmen understand the Canadian capital market structure and identify potential investment opportunities. You can sign up as a formal member with only $100. Application form is the following link: &lt;a href="contact.php"&gt;Contact Us&lt;/a&gt;. As a member of the CCCMAC, you can attend all the upcoming seminars for free and have an access to our global database.</p>
    </body>
    <photos>
        <photo>
            <i>1.jpg</i>
            <d>Mr.Meanchoff was answering questions regarding commercial real estate investment.</d>
        </photo>
        <photo>
            <i>2.jpg</i>
            <d>Mr.Meanchoff was speaking of commercial real estate investment.</d>
        </photo>
        <photo>
            <i>3.jpg</i>
            <d>An in-depth discussion</d>
        </photo>
        <photo>
            <i>4.jpg</i>
            <d>Mr. Shinobu was talking about senior housing trend in Canada.</d>
        </photo>
    </photos>
</event>
